TIFFANY DORRIS

Phone: 317-869-9990

Email: tiffanyvdorris@gmail.com

Mount Prospect, IL 60056

PROFILE

Enthusiastic and Dedicated worker who is always ready and willing for new challenges that come my way. With my 10 years of experience involving leadership and organization I've had a role in a variety of fields that have given me the ability to adapt and grow in various aspects; such as interpersonal and critical thinking. I find that my most recent experience has involved all of my years of work and has granted me the ability to succeed in many aspects such as teamwork, time management, and flexibility.

WORK HISTORY

Esthetician, Allure Skin & Laser; Elmhurst, IL 2021 - Present

- ◆ Perform esthetic procedures (i.e. Lasers and facials)
- Booking and organizing clients
- ◆ Manage Bookkeeping
- ◆ Ensure excellent and knowledgable experience for clients

Wax Specialist/Esthetician, European Wax Center; Skokie, IL 2018-2021

- ◆ Speed Waxing
- ◆ Meet and excel at sales goals
- ◆ Maintain regular clientele

Delivery & Sales fulfillment Associate, Home Depot, Indianapolis, IN 2016-2018

- ◆ Organize and Manage deliveries
- ◆ Operate all heavy machinery
- ◆ Host Project building events
- ◆ Train new associates in various departments

EDUCATION

Career foundry — UI Design 2023

Douglas J Aveda Institute — Licensed Esthetician, 2019

SKILLS

- **♦**Figma
- **♦**UI Design
- **♦**UX Research
- ◆HTML, Css, & Javascript
- ◆Esthetic Knowledge